<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bejeweled on MiniGameFun</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/minigamefun/categories/bejeweled/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bejeweled on MiniGameFun</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/minigamefun/categories/bejeweled/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Combo Snake</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/minigamefun/games/combo-snake-25210/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/minigamefun/games/combo-snake-25210/</guid>
      <description>Control the snake to move and collect gems. Collecting gems of the same color will create nodes of the corresponding color on the snakes body. When three nodes of the same color are connected, they will be automatically eliminated. Eliminating nodes can earn you extra points. Hitting the wall or colliding with itself will lead to the end of the game. Successfully eliminating the entire snakes body results in a game victory.&lt;br&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Instructions&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Computer Use the arrow keys to control Mobile phone Tap the screen to control the direction&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ratomilton Meets Sprunki Adventure</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/minigamefun/games/ratomilton-meets-sprunki-adventure-25211/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/minigamefun/games/ratomilton-meets-sprunki-adventure-25211/</guid>
      <description>Ratomilton Meets Sprunki is an exciting physics-based puzzle game where players must use their wits and strategic thinking to guide Rato Milton to his friend, Sprunki. Unlike Rato Milton, who depends on the environment to move, Sprunki stands completely still, waiting for Rato Milton to reach him. The challenge lies in manipulating the obstacles and objects in each level to set Rato Milton in motion, relying solely on physics and gravity to complete the journey. Gameplay Mechanics The game presents players with various levels filled with obstacles, platforms, and interactive objects. Rato Milton starts in a fixed position, and the only way t&lt;br&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Instructions&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;mouse only&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
