<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Soccer on MiniGameFun</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/minigamefun/categories/soccer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Soccer on MiniGameFun</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/minigamefun/categories/soccer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bubblehead Ball</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/minigamefun/games/bubblehead-ball-25382/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/minigamefun/games/bubblehead-ball-25382/</guid>
      <description>Are you a guy who is a talented with skills and speed? If yes, lets score. Bubblehead Ball is a thrilling and fast-paced football game where you can challenge your opponents and show your abilities. One more thing, all of our characters in game are not in football world. 1. Easy to control. 2. Funny characters. 3. Fantastic art. 4. Easy UX UI to access. Lets play and find out who they are.&lt;br&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Instructions&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using AD to move left or right W to jump J and K for taking shot&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tank Soccer Battle 1 2 3 4 Player</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/minigamefun/games/tank-soccer-battle-1-2-3-4-player-25450/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/minigamefun/games/tank-soccer-battle-1-2-3-4-player-25450/</guid>
      <description>Are you ready for a tank battle with your friends? A tank battle with a soccer ball! Bring your friends and fight with tanks.Fill up your tanks&amp;amp;amp;rsquo; ammunition and blow up all your friends&amp;amp;amp;rsquo; tanks. While blowing up your friends&amp;amp;amp;rsquo; tanks, don&amp;amp;amp;rsquo;t forget to shoot the soccer ball. The player who gets the soccer ball to the goal wins. You need to score a goal to win. Team up with your friend in a 2vs2 game and work together to score a goal.&lt;br&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Instructions&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Green Tank Use WASD to move and Q to fire Blue Tank Use Arrow Keys to move and P to fire Yellow Tank Use UHJK to move and M to fire Red Tank Use FCVB to move and N to fire&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
